[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 43, "question": "Did you enjoy the status of television icon?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "enjoy", "the", "status", "of", "television", "icon", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 44, "answer": "Sure.", "answer_tokens": ["Sure", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBZ", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 51, "question": "It's better than the alternative, right?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "better", "than", "the", "alternative", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 52, "answer": "It certainly is, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "certainly", "is", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Dick Van Dyke"]}, "docId": "111227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "NN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 57, "question": "Why you?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 58, "answer": "Well, I think it's sort of like -- I'm not comparing myself to Dick Van Dyke, but I think there's a characteristic that can help you survive in television which is a kind of an affability, and a vulnerability.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "it", "'s", "sort", "of", "like", "--", "I", "'m", "not", "comparing", "myself", "to", "Dick", "Van", "Dyke", ",", "but", "I", "think", "there", "'s", "a", "characteristic", "that", "can", "help", "you", "survive", "in", "television", "which", "is", "a", "kind", "of", "an", "affability", ",", "and", "a", "vulnerability", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 61, "question": "Oh, well, you know?", "question_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "well", ",", "you", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 62, "answer": "You're that guy.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "'re", "that", "guy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "IN", "PRP$", ":"], "qSentId": 73, "question": "How does it go down with all your famous friends?", "question_tokens": ["How", "does", "it", "go", "down", "with", "all", "your", "famous", "friends", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "RP", "IN", "DT", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 74, "answer": "Well, some of my --", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "some", "of", "my", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "IN", "JJS", "NN", "NN", "RB", "CC", "IN", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "VBG", "WP", "PRP", ":", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBZ", "WP", "DT", "JJ", "VBZ", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "NN", "NN", "WDT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "CC", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 75, "question": "Is it lonely out there?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "lonely", "out", "there", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "EX", "."], "aSentId": 76, "answer": "It's pretty lonely, but you know they seem to tolerate me somehow, because I can at least state myself eloquently and without actually kind of assuming what they -- the veneer of what they assume is what a Republican is, as some kind of nasty, strange villain that, you know, should be vilified and hated.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "pretty", "lonely", ",", "but", "you", "know", "they", "seem", "to", "tolerate", "me", "somehow", ",", "because", "I", "can", "at", "least", "state", "myself", "eloquently", "and", "without", "actually", "kind", "of", "assuming", "what", "they", "--", "the", "veneer", "of", "what", "they", "assume", "is", "what", "a", "Republican", "is", ",", "as", "some", "kind", "of", "nasty", ",", "strange", "villain", "that", ",", "you", "know", ",", "should", "be", "vilified", "and", "hated", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Tea Party"]}, "docId": "111227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "TO", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "JJ", "TO", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 88, "question": "ORGAN: Are you -- are you sympathetic to the Tea Party element of the Republicans or is that a step too far?", "question_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "Are", "you", "--", "are", "you", "sympathetic", "to", "the", "Tea", "Party", "element", "of", "the", "Republicans", "or", "is", "that", "a", "step", "too", "far", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "PRP", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "JJ", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNPS", "CC", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 89, "answer": "I'm sympathetic to some of the principles, but I'm not sure that the Tea Party has behavioral problem other than the ones that have been identified by people who are inimical to them.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "sympathetic", "to", "some", "of", "the", "principles", ",", "but", "I", "'m", "not", "sure", "that", "the", "Tea", "Party", "has", "behavioral", "problem", "other", "than", "the", "ones", "that", "have", "been", "identified", "by", "people", "who", "are", "inimical", "to", "them", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 93, "question": "Nothing they say be objectionable to you at all?", "question_tokens": ["Nothing", "they", "say", "be", "objectionable", "to", "you", "at", "all", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 94, "answer": "I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 103, "question": "Against gay marriage?", "question_tokens": ["Against", "gay", "marriage", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 104, "answer": "Against it, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Against", "it", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 108, "question": "I mean there are issues there, but you wouldn't agree with?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", "there", "are", "issues", "there", ",", "but", "you", "would", "n't", "agree", "with", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBP", "NNS", "RB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 109, "answer": "Absolutely yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 110, "question": "You played a famous gay character?", "question_tokens": ["You", "played", "a", "famous", "gay", "character", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 111, "answer": "Yes, I've played several.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "'ve", "played", "several", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Barack Obama"]}, "docId": "111227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 128, "question": "And did you buy into all the hope, the audacity, the stuff that he apparently came with?", "question_tokens": ["And", "did", "you", "buy", "into", "all", "the", "hope", ",", "the", "audacity", ",", "the", "stuff", "that", "he", "apparently", "came", "with", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 129, "answer": "Well, OK, I think Barack Obama's election is a milestone for this country and a wonderful thing.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "OK", ",", "I", "think", "Barack", "Obama", "'s", "election", "is", "a", "milestone", "for", "this", "country", "and", "a", "wonderful", "thing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 138, "question": "Isn't it incumbent on politicians, clearly president, to inspire their people?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "n't", "it", "incumbent", "on", "politicians", ",", "clearly", "president", ",", "to", "inspire", "their", "people", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNS", ",", "RB", "NN", ",", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 139, "answer": "Inspire, certainly.", "answer_tokens": ["Inspire", ",", "certainly", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 151, "question": "What is the simple answer?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "the", "simple", "answer", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 152, "answer": "Well, I would say greed.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "would", "say", "greed", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 157, "question": "Who do you like?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "do", "you", "like", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 158, "answer": "Right now I'm not gravitating toward a lot of people right now.", "answer_tokens": ["Right", "now", "I", "'m", "not", "gravitating", "toward", "a", "lot", "of", "people", "right", "now", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "WP", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 170, "question": "Who do you think is more electable?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "do", "you", "think", "is", "more", "electable", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBZ", "RBR", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 171, "answer": "If I were advising them, I would just tell them that they must inspire people to assume that they have a right to make their own decisions about what dreams they wish to dream.", "answer_tokens": ["If", "I", "were", "advising", "them", ",", "I", "would", "just", "tell", "them", "that", "they", "must", "inspire", "people", "to", "assume", "that", "they", "have", "a", "right", "to", "make", "their", "own", "decisions", "about", "what", "dreams", "they", "wish", "to", "dream", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 174, "question": "What was my dream?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "my", "dream", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 175, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 177, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 178, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "DT", "VBG", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 179, "question": "Nothing more glamorous than that?", "question_tokens": ["Nothing", "more", "glamorous", "than", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "JJR", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 180, "answer": "No, just wanted to be a working actor.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "just", "wanted", "to", "be", "a", "working", "actor", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "RBR", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 181, "question": "Have you fulfilled that?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "fulfilled", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 182, "answer": "Yes, I got a few more extras than I counted on.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "got", "a", "few", "more", "extras", "than", "I", "counted", "on", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 186, "question": "In terms of your acting aspirations, have you -- have you ticked all the boxes you wanted to tick?", "question_tokens": ["In", "terms", "of", "your", "acting", "aspirations", ",", "have", "you", "--", "have", "you", "ticked", "all", "the", "boxes", "you", "wanted", "to", "tick", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "PRP", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 187, "answer": "Not quite.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "quite", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "EX", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 188, "question": "What's left?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "left", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 189, "answer": "RAMMER: There's certainly a lot left.", "answer_tokens": ["RAMMER", ":", "There", "'s", "certainly", "a", "lot", "left", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBD", "RP", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", "TO", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 190, "question": "What's left on the acting block that you'd like to do?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "left", "on", "the", "acting", "block", "that", "you", "'d", "like", "to", "do", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 191, "answer": "Well, I started out wanting to be a dramatic actor, ended up being a comedic actor, and now I've gone back to being a dramatic actor now.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "started", "out", "wanting", "to", "be", "a", "dramatic", "actor", ",", "ended", "up", "being", "a", "comedic", "actor", ",", "and", "now", "I", "'ve", "gone", "back", "to", "being", "a", "dramatic", "actor", "now", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "NN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 195, "question": "If you -- if you have one role left to play, what would it be?", "question_tokens": ["If", "you", "--", "if", "you", "have", "one", "role", "left", "to", "play", ",", "what", "would", "it", "be", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "CD", "NN", "NN", "TO", "VB", ",", "WDT", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 196, "answer": "One role left to play.", "answer_tokens": ["One", "role", "left", "to", "play", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "``", "NNP", "''", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 203, "question": "What's the role?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "the", "role", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 204, "answer": "Because they say your character in \"Boss\" is very King Lear-esque.", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "they", "say", "your", "character", "in", "``", "Boss", "''", "is", "very", "King", "Lear-esque", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBZ", "DT", "RBS", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 219, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 220, "answer": "Iago is an interesting character because it's -- you know, it's the character that has the most words of any character in all the Shakespeare and it's almost every sentence is not iambic pentameter, it's iambic pentameter and a half.", "answer_tokens": ["Iago", "is", "an", "interesting", "character", "because", "it", "'s", "--", "you", "know", ",", "it", "'s", "the", "character", "that", "has", "the", "most", "words", "of", "any", "character", "in", "all", "the", "Shakespeare", "and", "it", "'s", "almost", "every", "sentence", "is", "not", "iambic", "pentameter", ",", "it", "'s", "iambic", "pentameter", "and", "a", "half", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 225, "question": "Is it just more fun being evil?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "just", "more", "fun", "being", "evil", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "JJR", "JJ", "VBG", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 226, "answer": "Sure.", "answer_tokens": ["Sure", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ":", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 227, "question": "It is, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["It", "is", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 228, "answer": "Yes -- no, it's a ball.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "--", "no", ",", "it", "'s", "a", "ball", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 244, "question": "What do you want from me?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "want", "from", "me", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 245, "answer": "You'll know when it comes up.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "'ll", "know", "when", "it", "comes", "up", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 253, "question": "So, you did do the hard yards of theatrical trainings, didn't you, to be a serious actor?", "question_tokens": ["So", ",", "you", "did", "do", "the", "hard", "yards", "of", "theatrical", "trainings", ",", "did", "n't", "you", ",", "to", "be", "a", "serious", "actor", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", ",", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 254, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Lawrence Olivier", "Gregory Peck"]}, "docId": "111227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 257, "question": "Who were the actors you looked up to?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "were", "the", "actors", "you", "looked", "up", "to", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "TO", "."], "aSentId": 258, "answer": "Gosh, Lawrence Olivier and Gregory Peck.", "answer_tokens": ["Gosh", ",", "Lawrence", "Olivier", "and", "Gregory", "Peck", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 262, "question": "Did you ever imagine at that stage, at Juilliard, you're looking around, all these talented people presumably -- did you ever imagine in your wildest dreams or maybe nightmares the level of fame that you would one day get through acting?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "ever", "imagine", "at", "that", "stage", ",", "at", "Juilliard", ",", "you", "'re", "looking", "around", ",", "all", "these", "talented", "people", "presumably", "--", "did", "you", "ever", "imagine", "in", "your", "wildest", "dreams", "or", "maybe", "nightmares", "the", "level", "of", "fame", "that", "you", "would", "one", "day", "get", "through", "acting", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", ",", "DT", "DT", "VBN", "NNS", "RB", ":", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", "CC", "VB", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "CD", "NN", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 263, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Juilliard"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "VB", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 270, "question": "Don't all actors doubt themselves?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "n't", "all", "actors", "doubt", "themselves", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 271, "answer": "And didn't always work really hard.", "answer_tokens": ["And", "did", "n't", "always", "work", "really", "hard", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 278, "question": "Well, that's -- that's sort of the flip side of narcissism, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["Well", ",", "that", "'s", "--", "that", "'s", "sort", "of", "the", "flip", "side", "of", "narcissism", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", ":", "IN", "POS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 279, "answer": "It is.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 299, "question": "In the back of your mind all you're thinking of is this could tank, and then what?", "question_tokens": ["In", "the", "back", "of", "your", "mind", "all", "you", "'re", "thinking", "of", "is", "this", "could", "tank", ",", "and", "then", "what", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "DT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "VBZ", "DT", "MD", "VB", ",", "CC", "RB", "WP", "."], "aSentId": 300, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 309, "question": "Do we go to a hole in the ice with this little corks filthy and then just start fishing?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "we", "go", "to", "a", "hole", "in", "the", "ice", "with", "this", "little", "corks", "filthy", "and", "then", "just", "start", "fishing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "JJ", "CC", "RB", "RB", "VB", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 310, "answer": "It's called an auger.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "called", "an", "auger", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 342, "question": "Are you any good at doing that yourself?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "any", "good", "at", "doing", "that", "yourself", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 343, "answer": "I'm probably OK at it.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "probably", "OK", "at", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "WP", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "WDT", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 344, "question": "What have you worked out about Kelsey Grammer?", "question_tokens": ["What", "have", "you", "worked", "out", "about", "Kelsey", "Grammer", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 345, "answer": "Kelsey Grammer is a guy who cares about people that has been trying to save the world because he couldn't save some things in his own life.", "answer_tokens": ["Kelsey", "Grammer", "is", "a", "guy", "who", "cares", "about", "people", "that", "has", "been", "trying", "to", "save", "the", "world", "because", "he", "could", "n't", "save", "some", "things", "in", "his", "own", "life", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Kelsey Grammer"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 405, "question": "You trained with him at the Juilliard, didn't you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "trained", "with", "him", "at", "the", "Juilliard", ",", "did", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 406, "answer": "RAMMER: Yes, we were together in school.", "answer_tokens": ["RAMMER", ":", "Yes", ",", "we", "were", "together", "in", "school", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 412, "question": "But it's probably -- it's part of that because you managed to deal with so many of the demons?", "question_tokens": ["But", "it", "'s", "probably", "--", "it", "'s", "part", "of", "that", "because", "you", "managed", "to", "deal", "with", "so", "many", "of", "the", "demons", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 413, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 420, "question": "I mean for a while, it must be fun, isn't it, despite everything else?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", "for", "a", "while", ",", "it", "must", "be", "fun", ",", "is", "n't", "it", ",", "despite", "everything", "else", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", ",", "IN", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 421, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "EX", "VBD", ":", "EX", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 432, "question": "What was the -- what was the wake-up moment for you?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "the", "--", "what", "was", "the", "wake-up", "moment", "for", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", ":", "WP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 433, "answer": "Well, there were -- there were several along the way.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "there", "were", "--", "there", "were", "several", "along", "the", "way", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Betty Ford"]}, "docId": "111227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VB", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "IN", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 438, "question": "How did you manage to stop in the end?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "you", "manage", "to", "stop", "in", "the", "end", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 439, "answer": "Well, actually, I did go to Betty Ford and that helped.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "actually", ",", "I", "did", "go", "to", "Betty", "Ford", "and", "that", "helped", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "RB", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 447, "question": "Do you drink alcohol?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "drink", "alcohol", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 448, "answer": "I have a drink sometimes, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "have", "a", "drink", "sometimes", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 449, "question": "You can drink in moderation?", "question_tokens": ["You", "can", "drink", "in", "moderation", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 450, "answer": "Yes, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 466, "question": "How did it feel to you?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "it", "feel", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 467, "answer": "It's interesting.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "interesting", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 503, "question": "Did she fire a gun at you?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "she", "fire", "a", "gun", "at", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 504, "answer": "That was another night.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "was", "another", "night", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "DT", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", ":", "DT", "VBZ", "WP", ":"], "qSentId": 507, "question": "ORGAN: You married her after she shot at you?", "question_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "You", "married", "her", "after", "she", "shot", "at", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 508, "answer": "Yes, no, this is the -- this is what --", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "no", ",", "this", "is", "the", "--", "this", "is", "what", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", ":", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 509, "question": "Wasn't that a warning sign, get off it?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "n't", "that", "a", "warning", "sign", ",", "get", "off", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "WDT", "DT", "VBG", "NN", ",", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 510, "answer": "I tell you, it was absurdly across -- a shot across the bow.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "tell", "you", ",", "it", "was", "absurdly", "across", "--", "a", "shot", "across", "the", "bow", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 511, "question": "A woman shoots at me, I'm thinking twice about the marriage, you know?", "question_tokens": ["A", "woman", "shoots", "at", "me", ",", "I", "'m", "thinking", "twice", "about", "the", "marriage", ",", "you", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 512, "answer": "So that fell apart pretty quickly.", "answer_tokens": ["So", "that", "fell", "apart", "pretty", "quickly", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", ",", "PRP$", ":", "``", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "TO", "PRP$", "."], "qSentId": 532, "question": "This must have been like hell, wasn't it?", "question_tokens": ["This", "must", "have", "been", "like", "hell", ",", "was", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 533, "answer": "Well, I have to -- I mean, I have to tell you, my -- \"The Real Housewives\" was my parting gift to her.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "have", "to", "--", "I", "mean", ",", "I", "have", "to", "tell", "you", ",", "my", "--", "``", "The", "Real", "Housewives", "''", "was", "my", "parting", "gift", "to", "her", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "VBD", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 550, "question": "Were you just charging around looking for true love and constantly believing you quickly found it?", "question_tokens": ["Were", "you", "just", "charging", "around", "looking", "for", "true", "love", "and", "constantly", "believing", "you", "quickly", "found", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 551, "answer": "No, I think -- I think what I was trying to do was sell it to myself.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "think", "--", "I", "think", "what", "I", "was", "trying", "to", "do", "was", "sell", "it", "to", "myself", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 561, "question": "But -- I mean, how are things?", "question_tokens": ["But", "--", "I", "mean", ",", "how", "are", "things", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 562, "answer": "Well, they're not good.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "they", "'re", "not", "good", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 563, "question": "Do you have any kind of dialogue with her?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "have", "any", "kind", "of", "dialogue", "with", "her", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "."], "aSentId": 564, "answer": "We have no contact, no.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "have", "no", "contact", ",", "no", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 572, "question": "How is your relationship with them?", "question_tokens": ["How", "is", "your", "relationship", "with", "them", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 573, "answer": "Oh, it's great.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "it", "'s", "great", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP$", "JJS", "TO", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NN", "WDT", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 576, "question": "You get plenty of access?", "question_tokens": ["You", "get", "plenty", "of", "access", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 577, "answer": "RAMMER: Well, they're trying to -- they're doing their best to actually kind of make that difficult for me right now.", "answer_tokens": ["RAMMER", ":", "Well", ",", "they", "'re", "trying", "to", "--", "they", "'re", "doing", "their", "best", "to", "actually", "kind", "of", "make", "that", "difficult", "for", "me", "right", "now", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 583, "question": "Do you think she married you because you were Kelsey Grammer, TV icon?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "she", "married", "you", "because", "you", "were", "Kelsey", "Grammer", ",", "TV", "icon", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 584, "answer": "No, I think she married me because I was Frasier.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "think", "she", "married", "me", "because", "I", "was", "Frasier", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Kelsey Grammer"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 585, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 586, "answer": "I think it was Frasier.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "was", "Frasier", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "RB", "RB", "MD", "VB", "NN", "WDT", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 596, "question": "What's been worst thing, the most hurtful thing she said about you?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "been", "worst", "thing", ",", "the", "most", "hurtful", "thing", "she", "said", "about", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 597, "answer": "Well, you know, I haven't been keeping track of everything, so there might be something that would surprise me.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "I", "have", "n't", "been", "keeping", "track", "of", "everything", ",", "so", "there", "might", "be", "something", "that", "would", "surprise", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 600, "question": "What's the most unfair labeling?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "the", "most", "unfair", "labeling", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 601, "answer": "She once said that I didn't want my daughter.", "answer_tokens": ["She", "once", "said", "that", "I", "did", "n't", "want", "my", "daughter", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 603, "question": "Yes, well, it would, wouldn't it?", "question_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "well", ",", "it", "would", ",", "would", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "MD", ",", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 604, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Los Angeles"]}, "docId": "111227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 655, "question": "To England from New York?", "question_tokens": ["To", "England", "from", "New", "York", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["TO", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 656, "answer": "From Los Angeles.", "answer_tokens": ["From", "Los", "Angeles", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["England", "New York"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 657, "question": "From Los Angeles?", "question_tokens": ["From", "Los", "Angeles", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 658, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Los Angeles"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Kayte"]}, "docId": "111227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 669, "question": "Well, you know what?", "question_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", "what", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "."], "aSentId": 670, "answer": "Because Kayte is a very beautiful young lady, as we can see here.", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "Kayte", "is", "a", "very", "beautiful", "young", "lady", ",", "as", "we", "can", "see", "here", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 700, "question": "Did she know who you were?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "she", "know", "who", "you", "were", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 701, "answer": "Oh, I think she knew who I was, but she didn't know who I am.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "I", "think", "she", "knew", "who", "I", "was", ",", "but", "she", "did", "n't", "know", "who", "I", "am", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 749, "question": "What is it about her you think that enabled her to deal with all this?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "it", "about", "her", "you", "think", "that", "enabled", "her", "to", "deal", "with", "all", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "VBN", "PRP$", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 750, "answer": "She believes in love.", "answer_tokens": ["She", "believes", "in", "love", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 775, "question": "Are you really enjoying it?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "really", "enjoying", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 776, "answer": "It's been -- it was a presumptive joy to go to work every day.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "been", "--", "it", "was", "a", "presumptive", "joy", "to", "go", "to", "work", "every", "day", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 786, "question": "Do you like him or not?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "like", "him", "or", "not", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 787, "answer": "I love him.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "love", "him", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 793, "question": "Isn't that you, in the end?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "n't", "that", "you", ",", "in", "the", "end", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "IN", "PRP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 794, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 815, "question": "Do you feel for the first you've gone back to the joy of life you had as a young boy?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "feel", "for", "the", "first", "you", "'ve", "gone", "back", "to", "the", "joy", "of", "life", "you", "had", "as", "a", "young", "boy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 816, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]